Teachers Union of the City of New York Records 5015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Educational Policy, internal and legislative, 1932-1948 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  Press release, pamphlet, reports, referendum ballot
- Educational Policy, 1941-1955 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  Reports, digest
- Elections, 1948-1950 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  Form letters, press release, ballots, slate of officers and executive board members
- Elections, 1951-1952 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  Form letters, ballots, envelopes
- Elections, 1954-1955 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  Ballots, press releases, form letter, report
- Elections, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, envelopes, notes, news clippings, ballots, acceptances and declinations, election results
- Elections, collective bargaining rep. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  Case, appeal, procedural background, report, pamphlet, photocopies, memo, correspondence, form letters
- Elementary School Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  Form letters, poster
- In re: Case of Stelle Eliashow, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Emergency Civil Liberties Union, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, publications, news clipping, memo, call to a conference
- Executive Board, 1956-1963 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  Press release, list of members of board, correspond form letters
- Executive Board, Dissolution, resolutions and minutes, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, form letter, resolution, minutes
- Executive Board, 1929-1930 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Executive Board, 1930-1931 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Executive Board, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Executive Board, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Executive Board, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Executive Board, 1932-1933 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Executive Board, 1933-1934 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Executive Board, 1934-1935 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Executive Board, 1935-1936 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Executive Board, 1937-1941 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Executive Board, 1944-1963 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Experimental School, 1924-1928 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, proposal, release, resume, memo, minutes, publication
- Feinberg Law, Appelate Divisions Case, 1949-1953 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  Briefs, appeal
- Feinberg Law, brief history and analysis of Feinberg Law and Supreme Court Decision, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  Release
- Feinberg Law, Case of Mary Daniman et al, 1949-1955 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  Pamphlets, briefs, appeals, petitions, correspondent
- Financial, 1940-1962 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  Audits, balance sheets, financial statements, correspondence, publication
- In re: Case of Mildred Flacks, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  Case; Foner Case See: Academic Freedom
- Forms, 1952-1955 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  Forms
- Case of David L. Friedman (incomplete), 1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Case of David L. Friedman, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Case of David L. Friedman, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Friedman Case, 1950 (Box 53-55)
- Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1953-1957 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, receipts, reports, newsletter
- In re: Case of Cyril Graze, 1952 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Hartley Committee Investigation, Samuel Wallach, replies to request to sign statement, 1948 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, form letters, telegrams; Hartley Committee Investigation See: Academic Freedom
- Health Insurance Plan, 1955-1961 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  An act, minutes, correspondence, insurance explanation and costs, news clippings
- Health Insurance Program, 1944 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, form letters, minutes
- Holiday disputes, 1928-1933 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, press releases
- In re: Philip Horowitz Case, 1953 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Illiteracy campaign, 1930 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  Correspondence; Informer Policy See: Board of Education
- Insurance, 1951-1952 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, statement, accident form
- International Committee for Political Prisoners, 1928 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- International Newspaper Printing Company, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Jansen's policy of November 8, closed #226, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  Telegram, correspondence, notes, report, interview, subpoenas; Jansen Resolution See: Academic Freedom
- Junior High School Committee, 1949-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, form letters, questionnaires, memo, statement, petition
- Junior High School Principals Association, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, program
- Juvenile Delinquency, 1943-1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  Publication, news clippings, survey, statements, resolution, form letter, report
- Juvenile Delinquency, Ad Hoc Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  Questionnaire, report, correspondence, news clippings
- Juvenile Deliquency, State Youth Commission, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  Release, news clippings, correspondence; Kaminsky Bill See: Legislation Kleinfeld Ricca Bill See: Legislation
- In re: Case of Hyman Koppelman, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  Report, exceptions to report
- In re: Case of Hyman Koppelman, case of insubordination, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Labor Relations, 1958-1961 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  Annual report, bulletins, news clippings, note
- Laboratory Assistants, 1957-1962 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  Memos, eligibility requirements, notes, news clippings
- Laboratory Assistants Committee, 1947-1954 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  Resolution, list of speakers, correspondence, form letters, press release, memo, telegram, news clippings, dollar facts; LaGuardia Economy Bill See: Legislation
- Abraham Lederman, Memorial Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, list of contributors, program
- Abraham Lederman Tribute, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  Program, press release, post cards, invitation, remarks, contract, correspondence, news clipping, order blank
- Abraham Lederman (President of T.U. Local 555) vs. Board of Education of City of New York, 1949-1951 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  Clippings, briefs, papers on appeal, cases, correspondence, news clippings
- Abraham Lederman et al vs. Board of Education, Exhibit file, 1948-1953 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  Court documents, correspondence; Lefkowitz Merit Bill See: Legislation
- Legal Relations, miscellaneous attorneys, 1951-1963 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  News clippings, bulletin, correspondence, legal paper
- Legal Relations, Leonard Boudin, 1954-1958 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Legal Relations, Herman E. Cooper, attorney reports, 1936-1939 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, reports
- Legal Relations, Royal W. Prance, 1949-1956 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  Correspondence, telegrams
- Legal Relations, Victor Rabinowitz and L. Boudin, 1954-1963 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Legal Relations, Witt and Cramer, 1949-1950 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, form letter, memo, case
- Legal Relations, Benjamin Zelman, 1949-1963 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  News releases, memos, correspondence, cases, news clippings, an act, form letters
- Legislation, Action Bulletins, 1956-1958 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  Bulletins, news clipping, circular
- Legislation, Action Bulletins, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  Bulletins, form letter
- Legislation, Action Bulletins, 1960-1963 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  Bulletins
- Legislation, Anti-informer, 1956-1958 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  Form letters, correspondence, news clippings
- Legislation, bills, general, 1959-1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  Bills, correspondence, clippings, memo
- Legislation, Memo on bills, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  Memos, clippings, legislative bills
- Legislation, Blease Bill, 1930 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Legislation, Briefs, statements, press releases, 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  Form letters, briefs, memos, press releases
- Legislation, Child labor and health, 1924-1937 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  Form letters, press releases, publication
- Legislation, civil rights, 1957-1960 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  Speech, correspondence, form letter
- Legislation, compensation law, 1930-1939 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Legislation, Condon-Wadlin Law, 1960-1963 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  Statements, correspondence, clippings, pamphlet, notice of public hearing, release
- Legislation, Condon-Wilson Bill, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Legislation, Congress, 1948-1950 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  Press release, resolution, telegrams, form letters, correspondence
- Legislation, Contractural tenure, 1953-1956 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  Correspondence, form letters, news clippings, an act
- Legislation, Corso Bill, Corporal punishment, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  Correspondence, form letters, memo, publication, news clippings, press release
- Legislation, Coughlin Bill, 1930 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  Correspondence, news clipping, press release, an act
- Legislation, Day Care (Nursery Schools), 1951-1957 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  Statement, bulletins, acts, form letter
- Legislation, Discrimination and Segregation, 1956-1957 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  Statement, form letter
- Legislation, Education, 1957-1959 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  News clippings, memo, acts, press release
- Legislation, Education Bill (Federal), 1924-1943 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Legislation, extra-curricular stoppage, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  Resolution, questionnaires, press releases, text of telegrams, news clippings, statement, circular, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, Federal aid to education, 1947-1948 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, statement
- Legislation, Federal aid to education, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, telegrams, press releases, publication, form letters
- Legislation, Federal aid to education, 1954-1955 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Legislation, Federal aid to Education, 1955-1956 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  news clippings
- Legislation, Federal aid to education, White House Conference, 1954-1956 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  Press releases, correspondence, news clipping
- Legislation, Feinberg Law, correspondence, 1949-1955 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  Statement, press release, circular, telegrams, post card, correspondence
- Legislation, Governor's message, 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, statements, comment
- Legislation, Governor's office, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  Message, press releases, correspondence, form letters, post cards
- Legislation, Governor's office (Harriman), 1956-1958 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  Press release, post cards, correspondence, form letters, telegrams
- Legislation, History (Higgins) Textbook Bill, 1921-1925 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  Correspondence, an act
- Legislation, Kaminsky Bill, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Legislation, Kleinfeld Ricca Bill, 1925-1931 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  Correspondence, press releases, injunction aid
- Legislation, Laboratory Assistants, 1945-1949 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  Brief, correspondence, memo, fact sheet
- Legislation, LaGuardia Economy Bill, 1932-1934 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  Correspondence, press release, telegrams, policy statement, form letter
- Legislation, Lefkovitz Merit Bill, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  Form letter, correspondence
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1930-1933 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1947-1950 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  Bulletins, correspondence, form letters, reports, statements, news clippings
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1945 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Statement, press release
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1946-1948 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  Telegrams, bulletins, briefs, budget proposals, statement, discussion, outline
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1949-1950 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  Receipt, statement, memo, bulletins, press releases, correspondence, form letters, tag
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  Form letters, correspondence, program, press release, comment, telegram
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  Press release, telegram, form letter, bulletin, not
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  Form letters, statement, bulletins, memos, press releases, news clippings
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1952-1955 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  Bulletins, press releases, memos, proposals, form letters
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1953-1958 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  Photocopies, receipt, telegrams, correspondence, form letters, bulletins, news clippings, interview, press releases
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1956-1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  Form letters, correspondence, post card, press releases, memos, bulletins
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  Press releases, bulletins, interview, form letters, correspondence
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  Form letters, correspondence, news clippings, list of state aid bills, bulletins, press releases
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, 1961 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  Release, correspondence, form letters, tag, news clippings
- Legislation, Legislative campaign, correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  Form letters, correspondence, memo
- Legislation, Legislators, correspondence, 1953-1962 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  Correspondence, form letters, note, press releases, telegram, memo
- Legislation, Mauhs Bill, 1949 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  Form letter, correspondence, an act, news clipping
- Legislation, memoranda on bills, 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Bulletins, form letters, correspondence memo, acts, press releases
- Legislation, memos to the Governor, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  Memos, legislative bill
- Legislation, Mundt-Nixon-Ferguson Bill, 1948-1950 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  Statement, resolution, memorandum, telegrams, bulletins, form letters, correspondence
- Legislation, N.Y.S. Council for Legislative Action, 1948-1949 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, form letters, notes, tentative plan
- Legislation, N.Y.S. Federation of Teachers Unions, 1936-1939 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  Notes, press releases, telegrams, statement, correspondence, form letter, newsletter
- Legislation, pension, 1951-1955 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, an act, memos, news clippings, form letters, press release, brief
- Legislation, pension and retirement, 1961-1962 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  Correspondence, legislative bills, memos, clippings, release
- Legislation, pension and retirement, 1956-1961 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, form letter, bulletins, Joint hearing, press releases, acts, summary, notes, memos, comments and calculations, news clippings
- Legislation, pension plan, 1960-1962 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  Clippings, correspondence, bills, forms, memo
- Legislation, professional practices, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Legislation, repressive (miscellaneous), 1949 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  Bulletin, press releases, statement, acts, telegrams, form letters, memo
- Legislation, salaries, statement to Jansen and Board of Education members, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, news clipping, statement
- Legislation, salary, 1947-1949 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  Correspondence, form letters, memo, telegrams, press releases, salary schedule, statement, bulletins
- Legislation, salary, 1958-1960 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, form letters, telegrams, an act, summary, table, press releases, statements, bulletins, news clippings
- Legislation, salary, briefs and statements, 1949-1951 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  Analysis, graph, statements, outline, resolution, memos, salary facts, correspondence, news clippings
- Legislation, salary, clippings, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Legislation, salary, extra-compensation, 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  Form letter, bulletin, correspondence, press releases, text of telegrams
- Legislation, salary, faculty actions, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  Telegrams, notes, press releases, post card, correspondence, form letters, news clipping
- Legislation, salary, Feinberg Salary Law, 1947-1951 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  Resolutions, rejection, memo, press release, bulletins, telegram, news clippings, tag, publication
- Legislation, salary Ford Fund survey on teachers salaries, 1954 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Legislation, salary, merit ratings, 1956-1962 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  List of arguments, telegram, pamphlet, news clippings correspondence
- Legislation, salary, mimeographed and printed, 1948-1950 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  Statement, comment, script, memo, fact sheet, press releases, petition, bulletins, analysis, telegram, open letter, ballots, correspondence, form letters, graphical report
- Legislation, salary, mimeographed and printed, 1953-1956 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  Instruction sheet, comment, bulletins, press releases, statements, resolution, post cards, correspondence, form letters, memos
- Legislation, salary, mimeographed and printed, 1956-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  Form letters, pledge, memo, press releases, criticism, statements, proposals, fact sheet
- Legislation, salary, single salary, 1956-1957 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  Brief, news clipping, correspondence
- Legislation, salary, Teachers Interest Committees (TIC) mailings to, 1952-1960 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  Bulletins, correspondence, form letters, post cards
- Legislation, school financing, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  News clippings, statements, legislative documents, correspondence, letters of transmittal
- Legislation, security risk, 1954-1959 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, form letter, legislative bill, clippings, pamphlet
- Legislation, social security, 1957 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  Bulletin, statement, correspondence
- Legislation, special subjects teachers campaign committee for maximum 25 period load, 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  Statement, telegrams, tentative brief, correspondence, tag
- Legislation, state aid to education, 1948-1955 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  Resolution, petition form, post cards, bulletin, correspondence, press releases, news clippings, memo, form letters
- Legislation, state aid to education, general, 1948-1949 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  News clipping, post cards, bulletins, telegrams, pamphlet, press release, outline, statements, resolutions, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, state aid to education, Albany delegation, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  News clipping, press release, bulletins, telegrams, form letter
- Legislation, state aid to education, 1950 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  Press release, outline, resolutions, comment, memo
- Legislation, state aid to education, Heald Commission, 1954-1956 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Legislation, state aid to education, 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  Brief, press releases, form letters, correspondence, report, remarks, summary
- Legislation, state aid to education, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  Copy of telegrams, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, state aid to education, 1962-1963 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  Resolutions, clippings, memo, telegrams, correspondence, form letter
- Legislation, state legislature, 1945-1950 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  Telegrams, memo, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, state organizing committee, general material, 1939-1954 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  Press release, minutes, memo, pamphlets, analysis, correspondence, form letters, bulletin
- Legislation, statute of limitations, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, memo, clippings
- Legislation, substitutes, 1946-1949 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  Resolutions, bulletins, memos, statements, press releases, brief, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, substitutes, 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  Memo, bulletin, telegrams, acts, news clippings, form letters, press release, correspondence
- Legislation, substitutes pension credit, Brydges La, 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  Correspondence, notes, bulletin, memos, circular
- Legislation, substitutes, service credit toward regular appointment, 10 year bill, 1955-1959 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  News clipping, memo, acts, correspondence, form let
- Legislation, substitute teachers campaign, list extension, 1937-1938 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  Bulletin, release, correspondence, leaflets, program, suggestions, question and answer sheet
- Legislation, Taft-Hartley, 1949 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  Memo, press release, correspondence, reports
- Legislation, T.U. program, 1952-1954 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  Proposals, bulletin
- Legislation, vacation pay, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  Case, correspondence
- Legislation, vocational schools commission, 1938-1940 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  Minutes, bulletin, suggestions, act, correspondence
- Legislation, salary, bonus, 1951 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Legislation, salary, budget, 1943-1945 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  Form letter, memos, bulletin, brief, resolution, statement, fact sheet
- Legislation, salary clippings, 1954 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  Bulletin, news clippings
- Legislation, salary, correspondence, 1947-1961 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  Memos, statements, brief, press releases, telegrams list of bills
- Legislation, salary, extra curricular stoppage, principal's report, 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  Correspondence, memo, photocopy
- Legislation, salary, faculty communications re: Unity, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Legislation, salary, grass roots, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  Telegram, form letters, analysis
- Legislation, salary, press releases, 1950-1955 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  Press releases, bulletin, correspondence, chart
- Legislation, salary, press releases, 1955-1960 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  Telegram, statement, correspondence, press releases
- Legislation, salary, schedules, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  Memo, statement, form letters, recommendations
- Legislation, salary campaign, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, telegram, statements, resolution
- Legislation, salary campaign, actions by faculty groups, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  Correspondence, form letters, telegrams, resolution bulletins, press releases, news clippings
- Legislation, salary campaign, Allen decision and Board of Education regulations (Greenfield Petition), 1951 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  Correspondence, form letters, press release, cases
- Legislation, salary campaign, Allen decision and Board of Education regulations, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, brief, statements, press releases, confidential material, speech
- Legislation, salary campaign, extra-curricular stoppage, Allen decision and "slave labor" regulation, 1951 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  Telegram, press releases, form letters, statement, bulletins
- Legislation, salary campaign, briefs, reports, etc, 1949-1950 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, form letters, open letters, memo, summary, brief, press releases, bulletins, telegram analysis, resolutions, statements, graph
- Legislation, salary campaign, briefs, statements, press releases, 1950-1951 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  Brief, salary facts, open letter, form letters, correspondence, memos, summaries, comments, bulletins, press releases, resolutions, statements
- Legislation, salary campaign, briefs, statement, releases, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  Resolution, press releases, statements, post cards bulletin, correspondence, form letters, fact sheet, questionnaire, salary scale, list of bills
- Legislation, salary campaign, 10 months pay, Brydges-Waters Bill, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  Memo, photocopy, correspondence, form letters
- Legislation, salary campaign, colleges, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  Form letter, bulletins
- Legislation, salary campaign, Committee for United Salary Action, 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  Press release, bulletins, form letters
- Legislation, salary campaign, correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  Correspondence, receipt, telegrams
- Legislation, salary campaign, correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Legislation, salary campaign, correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  Correspondence, speeches
- Legislation, salary campaign, "The facts behind the school salary crisis", 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  Pamphlets, form letters
- Legislation, salary campaign, faculty action, 1950-1951 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  Petitions, telegrams, press release, resolutions, form letters
- Legislation, salary campaign, faculty and T.I.C. action, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  Correspondence, form letters, questionnaires, telegrams, ballot
- Legislation, salary campaign, grassroots, 1954-1955 (Box 68, Folder 11)